

## 0049 1725602848

@ Sajedeh.n219@gmail.com

in sajedeh-nasiri

sajedehnasiri.github.io

## **About Me**

I'm a designer. My background in technology and art has allowed me to bring a diverse perspective to my work, whether designing robots or creating digital solutions to improve daily life. With my experience and dedication, I am confident in my ability to impact any project positively.

## **Skills**

User Interface Design
User Experience Design
Interaction Design
Visual Design
User Research and Analysis
Information Architecture
User Testing
Prototyping
Wireframing
Usability Testing
Heuristic Evaluation
Figma
Adobe Illustrator
Adobe Photoshop
Unity 2D

# **Education**

#### **UI/UX** in Action

UXland , Seattle , US May 2022 - Jul 2022

# Fundamental of User Experience

UXland, Seattle, US Aug 2022 - Oct 2022

# Bachelor of Robotics Engineering

Azad University Tehran , Iran, 2015-2019

# **Job Experiences**

## Visual Designer (Remote Job)

Aug. 2023 - now

Toyabo, Hochheim am Main, Germany

- Created visual assets, including icons, infographics, animations, and social media content for various platforms.
- Designed and produced marketing collaterals including flyers, brochures, vouchers, and posters.

### **UI Designer** (Freelance Job)

Jan. 2024 - now

Evangelische-allianz-magdeburg, Magdeburg, Germany

- Redesigned the website and implemented new pages.
- Deliverable includes heuristic evaluation of the current site, competitive research, site map, and low to High-fidelity wireframes.

### **UX/UI Designer** (Freelance Job)

June 2023 - Nov. 2023

Indexturant, Dubai, UAE

- Created interactive prototypes, low to High-fidelity wireframes, logic flows, and visual design.
- Provided content strategy based on market research, and usability testing to enhance user experience.

## **UX/UI Teacher Assistant** (Volunteer Job)

Nov. 2022 - now

UXland, Seattle, US

- Guided and monitored student progress, delivering feedback and guidance for project development.
- Mentored students with a primary emphasis on mastering the Figma software, fostering proficiency and expertise in design tools.
- Supervised and directed classroom activities, ensuring a structured and effective learning environment.

## **Robotic and programming Teacher**

Sep. 2017 - Dec. 2021

FIRA ROBOschool, Tehran, Iran

- Developed a comprehensive lesson plan tailored for students aged 9-15, covering programming, mechanics, and electronics.
- Instructed and guided students through hands-on activities, fostering their creativity and helping them bring their ideas to fruition.

# **Courses and Certifications**

Gamification | Inverse School | 2023

Advanced UI (Prototyping) | UXland | 2023

Stop Motion Techniques | Inverse School | 2020

Fundamentals of 2D Animate | Inverse School | 2020

Creating Story Board for Animations | Inverse School | 2020

Artificial Intelligence & Machine Learning | Tehran University | 2019

Python programming | Tehran University | 2018